Guide to the Zelda Fichandler papers, 1950-2000
George Mason University Libraries
- Zelda Fichandler papers
  - "A History of American Film", Broadway production (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - "Moon Children", contract agreements (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - "Dancing at Lughnasa", contract information (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - "A Community Carol", contract information (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - "The Price", contract information (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - "A Small World", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - "The Revengers' Comedies", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - "A Room of Ones Own", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 14)
  - special projects with the African American Company (Box 192, Folder 14)
  - "Fires in the Mirror", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 15)
  - "Perfect Ganesh", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 16)
  - "The Obyssey", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 17)
  - "A Long Day's Journey into Night", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 18)
  - "Hedda Gabler", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 19)
  - "I am a Man", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 20)
  - "What the Butler Saw", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 21)
  - "A Month in the Country", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 22)
  - "Life go Boom", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 23)
  - "Almost Blue", contract and royalty information (Box 192, Folder 24)
  - Thomas Fichandler sympathy notes and memorials, 1997 (Box 192, Folder 25)
  - "The Cage", financial information (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - "Dandilion Wine", financial information (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - royalty income, 1980-1981 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - "Catsplay", financial information (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - "Little Theatre of the Deaf", financial information (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - "Sizwe Banzi", financial information (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - "Comden and Green", financial information (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - "Boccaccio", financial information (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - "I am a Women", financial information (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Cronyn/Tandy, financial information (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - "Jacques Brel", financial information (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - "Oba Koso", financial information (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - "Oh What a Lovely War", financial information (Box 193, Folder 13)
  - "The Lonesome Train", financial information (Box 193, Folder 14)
  - "Susuki", financial information (Box 193, Folder 15)
  - "Montieth and Rand", financial information (Box 193, Folder 16)
  - "Starting here and Starting now", financial information (Box 193, Folder 17)
  - "Jar the Floor", financial information (Box 193, Folder 18)
  - "The Time of Your Life", financial information (Box 193, Folder 19)
  - "Yerma", financial information (Box 193, Folder 20)
  - "School for Wives", financial information (Box 193, Folder 21)
  - "trinidad Sisters", financial information (Box 193, Folder 22)
  - "Mrs. Klein", financial information (Box 193, Folder 23)
  - "The Visit", financial information (Box 193, Folder 24)
  - "The Father", financial information (Box 193, Folder 25)
  - "Of Thee I Sing", financial information (Box 193, Folder 26)
  - "Way of the World", financial information (Box 193, Folder 27)
  - audition lists, 1960's (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - audition lists, 1970's (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - auditions 1973 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - 0notes on 1989-1990 season (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - 1989-1990 season, notes and correspondence (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - costume designers resumes (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - lighting designers resumes (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - scenic designers resumes (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - cultural diversity NEA grants infomation, photo book of Zelda (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - production ideas; 1973-1975 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - ideas and possibilities (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - misc. notes on plays (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - list of plays and agents; late 1960's (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - list of production ideas, 1960's (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - misc. plays and ideas, 1960's (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - 1969-1970 season list (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - 1977-1978 season list and notes (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - 1981-1982 season list (Box 196, Folder 9)
  - 1982-1983 season blurbs (Box 196, Folder 10)
  - 1983-1984 season planning notes (Box 196, Folder 11)
  - 1984-1985 season blurbs (Box 196, Folder 12)
  - 1985-1986 season blurbs (Box 196, Folder 13)
  - 1987-1988 season playlists (Box 196, Folder 14)
  - 1988-1989 season list (Box 196, Folder 15)
  - auditions 1969 (Box 196, Folder 16)
  - auditions 1971 (Box 196, Folder 17)
  - auditions - 1972 (Box 196, Folder 18)
  - American Theatre Association correspondence, 1975 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - The American Assembly event, 1977 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - The American Assembly report on performing arts, 1977 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - speeches; US-Soviet relations, and the performing arts (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - correspondence regarding airplane noise, 1972 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - letters of contracts; 1983 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Terry Currier, 1984 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - audience responses 1985 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - audience responses; 1985 (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: Boston University (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - audience response; 1980 (Box 197, Folder 11)
  - "The Champeen", correspondence,1974 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - "The Championship Season", playbill and correspondece, 1973 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - "The Changeling", article and notes, 1985 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - "The Changing Room", correspondence and playbill, 1972 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - "Harry Chapin:Lies and Legends", correspondence and playbill, 1984 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - "The Charlatan", program (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - "Checkmates", articles (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - "The Chemmy Circle", correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - "The Cherry Orchard", lit. materials (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - "The Cherry Orchard", playbill and reviews (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - "The Cherry Orchard", correspondence and reviews, 1988 (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - "Chez Nous", correspondence, 1974 (Box 198, Folder 12)
  - "Chicago city limits, Blizzard of '81", playbill (Box 198, Folder 13)
  - "The Cheif Thing", correspondence and notes (Box 198, Folder 14)
  - "The Chief Thing", script (Box 198, Folder 15)
  - "The Child", cast list, notes and correspondence (Box 198, Folder 16)
  - "Children", correspondence and review (Box 198, Folder 17)
  - "Children of a Lesser God", playbill (Box 198, Folder 18)
  - "Children of the Arbat", article (Box 198, Folder 19)
  - "Children of the Sun", article (Box 198, Folder 20)
  - "The Chinese Wall", article (Box 198, Folder 21)
  - "Chip off Olympus", correspondence (Box 198, Folder 22)
  - "A Chorus Line", playbill (Box 198, Folder 23)
  - "A Chorus of Disapproval", correspondence, article, schdule, notes (Box 198, Folder 24)
  - casting sheet, 1968-1972 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - casting sheets (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - list of actors used during the first 5 seasons, 1950-1955 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: acting company, 62'-63' (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - correspondence: acting company 1963-1964 (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - correspondence: The Acting Company, 1964-1965 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - misc correspondence with actors; 1960's (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - correspondence with actors; 1960's (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - actors profiles; 1960's (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - correspondence: black actors in California (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - "The Cavern", article (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - "Caucasian Chalk Circle", notes, articles and correspondence (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - "Ceremonies in Dark of Men", playbill (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - "The Causcasian Chalk Circle", notes, playbills and reviews (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - "Catsplay", script (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - "Catsplay", correspondence and reviews (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - "Cats", playbill (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof", script and review (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - "Catch-22", playbill, press release and review (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - "Casualties", review and sch. (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - "castways", playbill (Box 200, Folder 11)
  - "The Castle", press releases (Box 200, Folder 12)
  - audience responses (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - audience response letters (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - ticket stub on a napkin (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - correspondence: George Hatza (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Jan Kubicki notes (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - misc. letters (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - correspondence: Boston University (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - An Acting Workshop notes (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - misc. notes (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - misc. notes (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - "Carmen", playbill and review (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - "Career", correspondence, 1957 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - "The Caretaker", playbill and reviews (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - "Captain Jinks of the Horse Marines", cast list, notes (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - "Candide", notes, production information (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - "The Cage", correspondence, playbills and reviews (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - "Camp Meeting", partial script and playbill (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - "Camino Real", correspondence (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - "Camino Real", press release (Box 202, Folder 9)
  - "Camille", program (Box 202, Folder 10)
  - "Cafe Crown", playbill (Box 202, Folder 11)
  - "Cabrona", script (Box 202, Folder 12)
  - "Cabrona", script, cast list and audience response cards (Box 202, Folder 13)
  - "By Strouse", reviews (Box 202, Folder 14)
  - "Butley", playbill (Box 202, Folder 15)
  - "Busy Dyin'", production notes and correspondence (Box 202, Folder 16)
  - "Charles Busch: Alone in a Cast of Thousands", review and correspondence (Box 202, Folder 17)
  - "Buried Child", playbill, correspondence, notes and research (Box 202, Folder 18)
  - "Boys in the Band", playbill, reviews and correspondence (Box 202, Folder 19)
  - "Boy Meets Girl", research (Box 202, Folder 20)
  - "Bread and Puppet Theatre", information and article (Box 202, Folder 21)
  - "Brecht on Brecht", playbill and correspondence (Box 202, Folder 22)
  - "briar Patch", reviews and cast list (Box 202, Folder 23)
  - "Brilliant Traces", review (Box 202, Folder 24)
  - "Broadway", correspondence (Box 202, Folder 25)
  - "The Brownsville Raid", program and reviews (Box 202, Folder 26)
  - "The Brothers Karamozov", correspondence (Box 202, Folder 27)
  - "Waltz of the Toreadors",press release (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - "Voyage", correspondence (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - "Vivat/Vivat Regina", playbill (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - "Visotsky", reviews, information etc... (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - "The Visit", playbills, reviews, notes and production information (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - "The Visit", playbills, reviews, notes and production information (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - "Village Heros", playbill and correspondence (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - "Vienna" Lusthaus", playbill (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - "Victory over the Sun", playbill (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - "Veterans", correspondence and reviews (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - "Vanities", playbill (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - "Vampires in Kodachrome", script and notes (Box 203, Folder 12)
  - "Unwished for Happiness", correspondence (Box 203, Folder 13)
  - "Vamps and Rideouts", correspondence, playbill and production information (Box 203, Folder 14)
  - "USA", correspondence, playbill and misc. notes (Box 203, Folder 15)
  - "Uptight", correspondence, playbill and reviews (Box 203, Folder 16)
  - "Up from Paradise", playbill (Box 203, Folder 17)
  - "When we Dead Awaken", playbill (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - "What the Babe Said" and "Total Recall", audience responses, performance reports (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - "When the Pussywillows Bloom in Wilton", correspondence (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - "When You Comin Back Red Ryder?", playbill and correspondence (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - "Where has Tommy Flowers Gone?", correspondence (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - "Where Memories are Magic", correspondence and review (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - "Whiskey", correspondence (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - "White Horse, Black Horse", correspondence (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - "Whoopie Goldberg", playbill and review (Box 204, Folder 9)
  - "Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?", playbills and reviews (Box 204, Folder 10)
  - "The Wild Duck", cast list, playbills, reviews and misc. production notes (Box 204, Folder 11)
  - Russian Arts Festival Trip; Play bills, Correspondence, Post cards, Contact lists (Box 205, Folder 1)
    Most material in Russian
  - Russian Arts Festival Trip; Reviews and News Articles (Box 205, Folder 2)
    Material in Russian
  - Actors Equity Association: Correspondence, 1952-1957 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Actors Equity Association: Paper, "Shakespeare the Humanist"; Russian Program; Correspondence (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Actors Equity Association: Correspondence, 1957-1965; News articles (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Actors Equity Association: Misc. Correspondence (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Untitled Paper: Carbon paper labeled "Chapter II" (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - Misc Correspondence; News articles on "Art and Life"; 1964 World Theater program (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - Misc news articles on "Art and Life"; Misc notes (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - Misc news articles on "Art and Life"; Misc notes (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - Bibliography: Sources in Russian (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Untitled Paper: Labeled "Chapter IV" (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Untitled Paper: Labeled "Chapter III" (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - Untitled Paper: Labeled "Chapter IV" (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Misc. news articles: labeled "Playwrights" (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Misc notes, correspondence, and news articles: labeled "Acting Method and Style" (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - "Theory and Technique of Playwriting": Paper by John Howard Lawson (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Misc news articles and correspondence; World Theater Program (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - Misc news articles and correspondence: National Shakespeare Festival program (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - Misc correspondence and announcements; Black and White photos (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - "Theater of the Little Hand": Misc Correspondence, Playbill for "Hansel and Gretel" (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Misc correspondence and news articles: labeled "Children's Events" (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Misc Correspondence, news articles, and programs: labeled "Special Events - Dance" (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - Misc news articles, notes and programs: labeled "Special Events - Music" (Box 206, Folder 14)
  - Misc theater festival schedules: labeled "Repertory - Systems" (Box 206, Folder 15)
  - Misc correspondence, news articles, and programs: labeled "Special Events - small skits etc." (Box 206, Folder 16)
  - Misc. correspondence and check lists: labeled "New Building" (Box 206, Folder 17)
  - correspondence on educational programing, 1960-1961 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - misc. correspondence, 1960-1976 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - misc. files including The Acting Company information (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - historical notes and correspondence (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - NYU information (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - personal effects from Russian Tour 1973 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - NEA Theatre grant information (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - new building construction information (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Snow Speech and others (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - Russia Take 2 (Box 207, Folder 10)
  - misc. correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - misc. correspondence, 1976-1982 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - box office reports and capacity information; 1980-1981 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - misc. correspondence and notes (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - audience response letters (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - audience responses (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - audience responses (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - audience responses (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - audience responses (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - audience responses (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - personal (Box 209, Folder 6)